好的，大家好，我今天要谈论这篇文章
all right hello everyone I'm today going
to talk about this paper about how
Facebook使用Memcache是​​为了处理巨大的负载
Facebook uses memcache I'm in order to
handle enormous load the reason we're
阅读本文是因为这是一份经验论文，实际上没有任何内容
reading this paper is that it's an
experience paper there's not really any
这里有新的概念，想法或技术，但这有点像是真实的生活
new concepts or ideas or techniques here
but it's kind of what a real live
公司在尝试建立非常高的容量时遇到了麻烦
company ran into when they were trying
to build very high capacity
基础设施您可以通过多种方式阅读它，一种是
infrastructure there's a couple of ways
you could read it one is a sort of
关于如果您不认真对待一致性会出问题的警告性故事
cautionary tale about what goes wrong if
you don't take consistency seriously
从一开始，另一种阅读方式就是关于这
from the start another way to read it is
that it's an impressive story about how
通过使用大多数现成的软件获得极高的容量
to get extremely high capacity from
using mostly off-the-shelf software
另一种阅读方式是它是一种说明或基本
another way to read it is that it's a
kind of illustration or the fundamental
在试图变得很高之间，很多设置都面临着挣扎
struggle that a lot of setups face
between trying to get very high
通过复制等方法以及如何保持一致性来实现的性能
performance which you do by things like
replication and how to give consistency
像复制这样的技术真的是敌人，所以你知道我们
for which techniques like replication
are really the enemy and so you know we
可以争论我们是否喜欢他们的设计，还是认为它是优雅的还是
can argue about whether we like their
design or we think it's elegant or a
很好的解决方案，但我们不能真正与他们取得的成功争论不休，因此
good solution but we can't really argue
with how successful they've been so we
确实需要认真对待它们，对我来说，实际上我首先
do need to take them seriously and for
me actually this paper which I first
读了很多年前，我一直在想这件事，
read quite a few years ago it's been I
thought about it a lot and it's been
各种各样的想法和对问题的理解的来源
sort of a source of sort of ideas and
understanding about problems at many
点数
points
好的，所以在适当谈论Facebook之前，您知道他们是
all right so before talking about
Facebook proper you know they're an
您经常看到或有很多人拥有的模式示例
example of a pattern that you see fairly
often or that many people have
他们尝试建立网站来做某事的经验丰富，而您
experienced in which they're trying to
build a website to do something and you
通常知道建立网站的人对建立高级网站不感兴趣
know typically people who build websites
are not interested in building high
您知道的高性能高性能存储基础架构
performance you know high performance
storage infrastructure they're
对构建使用户满意或出售的功能感兴趣
interested in building features that
will make their users happy or selling
更多广告或您所知道的东西，所以它们不会以
more advertisements or something you
know so they they're not gonna start by
花大量的时间或大量的时间来建立自己的风格
spending a main year of effort or a
whole lot of time building cool
他们将首先构建基础设施，然后对其进行排序
infrastructure they're gonna start by
building features in that they'll sort
仅在他们真正必须做到的范围内使基础设施更好
of make infrastructure better only to
the extent that they really have to
因为你知道那是他们时间的最佳利用，所以这是一个典型的开始
because you know that's the best use of
their time alright so a typical starting
一个网站很小的情况下的场景，您知道没有
scenario in a ways when a some website
is very small is you know there's no
不仅可以从一台机器开始，还可以
point in starting with anything more
than just a single machine right you
知道也许您刚开始时只有几个用户坐在他们前面
know maybe you started you only have a
couple users sitting in front of their
浏览器，您知道他们在这里与您的单机通过Internet进行通信
browsers and you know they talk over the
internet here with your single machine
您的单台计算机可能现在要运行Apache Web服务器，也许您
your single machine is gonna maybe run
the Apache web server now maybe you
使用PHP或Python或其他一些语言编写用于生成网页的脚本
write the scripts that produce web pages
using PHP or Python or some other
方便，易于编程的脚本风格语言和Facebook
convenient easy to program sort of
scripting style language and Facebook
使用PHP，您需要将数据存储在某个地方，也可以下载排序
uses PHP you need to store your data
somewhere or you can just download sort
的标准数据库和Facebook碰巧使用了我的续集，我的学校很好
of standard database and Facebook happen
to use my sequel my school is a good
选择，因为它实现了续集查询语言，功能非常强大且功能强大
choice because it implements the sequel
query language is very powerful and acid
事务提供了持久的存储，所以这就像一个非常好的设置
transactions provides durable storage so
this is like a very very nice set up I
其实我会带你走很长一段路，但是假设你成功了
am will take you a long way actually but
supposing supposing you get successful
您获得越来越多的用户，您知道您将获得越来越多的负载
you get more and more users you know
you're gonna get more and more load more
越来越多的人将浏览您的网站并运行任何PHP东西
and more people gonna be viewing your
website and running whatever PHP stuff
您可以使用网站提供的内容，因此在某些时候
you're with
site provides and so at some point
几乎可以肯定，第一个出错的地方是PHP
almost certainly the first thing that's
going to go wrong is that the PHP
脚本会占用过多的CPU时间，这通常是第一个瓶颈
scripts are gonna take up too much CPU
time that's usually the first bottleneck
如果他们从单个服务器开始，人们就会遇到，所以您需要的是一些
people encounter if they start with a
single server so what you need is some
为您的PHP脚本获得更多功能的方法，这使我们能够
way to get more horsepower for your PHP
scripts and so that takes us to kind of
您知道其中有很多网站的网站的第二架构
architecture number two for websites in
which you know you have lots and lots of
比以前需要更多CPU功能的用户数量更多的用户
users right or more users than before
you need more CPU power for your PHP
脚本，因此您可以运行一堆前端服务器，其唯一的工作就是运行Web
scripts so you run a bunch of front end
servers whose only job is to run the web
用户浏览器与之通信的服务器，这些服务器称为前端服务器，因此
servers that users browsers talk to and
these are called front end servers so
这些都将运行补丁
these are going to run a patch either
网络服务器和PHP脚本现在您知道用户将要与之交谈
webserver and the PHP scripts now you
know you users are going to talk to
在不同时间使用不同的服务器，也许您的用户将彼此正交
different servers at different times
maybe your users Quadra each other they
互相发消息，他们需要对方的信息或其他内容
message each other they need to see each
other's posts or something
因此所有这些前端服务器都需要查看相同的后端数据
so all these front-end servers are going
to need to see the same back-end data
为了做到这一点，您可能至少只能坚持一会儿
and in order to do that you probably
can't just stick at least for a while
您可以只使用一个数据库服务器，这样您就可以拥有一个
you can just stick with one database
server so you gonna have a single
机器已经是我处理所有数据库所有查询的续集，并且
machine already my sequel that handles
all of the database all queries and
更新从前端服务器读取和写入，如果可以的话，
updates reads and writes from the front
end servers and if you possibly can it's
明智的做法是在这里使用一台服务器，因为一旦您使用两台服务器，
wise to use a single server here because
as soon as you go with two servers and
以某种方式，您在多个数据库服务器上的数据变得更加复杂
somehow your data over multiple database
servers like gets much more complicated
您需要担心是否需要分布式交易或
and you need to worry about things like
do you need distributed transactions or
它如何使用PHP脚本决定与哪个数据库服务器进行通讯，等等
how it has the PHP scripts decide which
database server to talk to and so again
使用第二种架构，您可以获得很长的路要走
you can get a long way with this second
architecture you have as much CPU power
您可以根据需要添加更多前端服务器，最多可以添加一个
as you like by adding more front end
servers and up to a point a single
数据库服务器实际上将能够吸收许多前端的原因权限
database server will actually be able to
absorb the reason rights of many front
结束，但您知道您可能会非常成功，您会获得更多用户，并且
ends but you know maybe you're very
successful you get even more users and
所以问题是接下来会出什么问题，通常接下来会出什么问题
so the question is what's gonna go wrong
next and typically what goes wrong next
是数据库服务器，因为您总是可以添加更多CPU和更多Web服务器
is that the database server since you
can always add more CPU more web servers
您知道不可避免的错误是数据库服务器过了一段时间
you know what inevitably goes wrong is
that after a while the database server
用完了好吧，这是网络的下一个架构是什么
runs out of steam okay so what's the
next architecture this is web
建筑3和大型网站的标准演变方式
architecture 3 and the kind of standard
evolution of big websites here we have
如果您现在知道成千上万的用户，而且很多
the same if you know now thousands and
thousands of users lots and lots of
前端，现在我们基本上我们知道我们将不得不拥有多个
front ends and now we basically we know
we're gonna have to have multiple
数据库服务器，所以现在在前端后面，我们拥有一整套数据库
database servers so now behind the front
ends we have a whole rack of database
服务器每个人再次运行我的续集
servers each one of them running my
sequel again
但是我们将分片现在驱动的数据以分片数据
but we're going to shard the data
we're driven now to sharding the data
通过数据库服务器，所以您可能知道第一个拥有您知道的密钥
over the database server so you know
maybe the first one holds keys you know
a到G＆G到第二个，按住G到Q，你知道
a through G & G through second one holds
keys G through Q and you know whatever
图表恰好是现在，您知道要教的前端
the charting happens to be and now the
front-end you know you have to teach
您的PHP脚本在这里查看它们所需的数据并尝试找出
your PHP scripts here to look at the
data they need and try to figure out
他们将在不同时间与之交谈的数据库服务器
which database server they're going to
talk to it you know in different times
对于不同的数据，他们将与不同的服务器通信，因此这是分片的
for different data they're going to talk
to different servers so this is sharding
当然，之所以能为您带来帮助，是因为现在所有的工作
and of course the reason why this gives
you a boost is that now the all the work
阅读和写作的分裂，希望可以平均地分裂
of reading and writing has split up
hopefully hopefully evenly split up
在这些服务器之间，因为它们保存不同的数据，所以现在可以复制评级字
between these servers since they hold
different data now replicas rating word
绘制数据图表，它们可以并行执行并具有很大的并行度
charting the data and they can execute
in parallel and have big parallel
读取和写入数据的能力，PHP代码必须要痛苦一些
capacity to read and write data it's a
little bit painful the PHP code has to
如果更改了以下数据库服务器的设置，则了解分片
know about the sharding if you change
the setup of the database servers that
您添加了新的数据库服务器，或者您意识到需要拆分密钥
you add a new database server or you
realize you need to split up the keys
不同的是，您知道现在需要一个软件，您将不得不修改该软件
differently you know now you need a
you're gonna have to modify the software
运行在前端或其他东西上，以便他们了解
running on the front ends or something
in order for them to understand about
如何切换到新的分片所以这里有些痛
how to cut over to the new sharding so
there's some there's some pain here
还有是否需要交易，如果您知道很多人会使用它们
there's also if you need transactions
and you know many people use them if you
需要交易，但单笔交易中涉及的数据超过
need transactions but the data involved
in a single transaction is on more than
一台数据库服务器，您可能需要两阶段提交或一些
one database server you're probably
going to need two-phase commit or some
其他分布式交易方案也很痛苦，也很慢
other distributed transaction scheme
it's also a pain and slow all right well
您可以通过这种安排走得很远，但是这很昂贵
you can you can get fairly far with this
arrangement however it's quite expensive
我的续集或你们中的一些人知道功能全面的数据库服务器，例如人
my sequel or sort of you know fully
featured database servers like people
喜欢使用它不是特别快，它可能可以
like to use it's not particularly fast
it can probably
每秒执行数十万次读取，权限大大减少，您
perform a couple hundred thousand reads
per second and far fewer rights and you
知道网站的阅读往往很繁琐，所以很可能您会耗尽
know web sites tend to be read heavy so
it's likely that you're gonna run out of
写入之前先进行读取，流量将是我们在网络上加载的流量
steam for reads before writes that
traffic will be that we load on the web
服务器将由读取为主，因此一段时间后，您就可以切片
servers will be dominated by reads and
so after a while you know you can slice
越来越多的服务器上的数据越来越稀薄，但是有两件事出错了
the data more and more thinly over more
and more servers but two things go wrong
与那个是一些有时你是你有特定的关键是
with that one is that the some sometimes
you're you have specific keys that are
经常使用的热食，没有多少切片的确有帮助，因为每个
hot that are used a lot and no amount of
slicing really helps there because each
密钥仅在单个服务器上，因此非常流行，服务器可以
key is only on a single server so that
keeps very popular that servers can be
无论您对数据进行了多少分区或分片，
overloaded no matter how much you
partition or shard the data and the
添加的另一个问题是缩短添加很多续集
other problem with adding was shorting
adding lots and lots of my sequel
用于分片的数据库服务器的确是一种昂贵的方式
database servers for sharding is that
it's really an expensive way to go as it
事实证明，经过一点之后，您将开始思考得很好
turns out and after a point you're gonna
you're going to start to think that well
而不是花很多钱来添加另一个运行我的数据库服务器
instead of spending a lot of money to
add another database server running my
续集我可以让同一台服务器在它上面运行得更快
sequel I could take the same server run
something much faster on it like as it
发生Memcache D，并且每秒获得更多读取
happens memcache D and get a lot more
reads per second out of the same
使用缓存而不是使用数据库的硬件，因此下一个架构和
Hardware using caching than using
databases so the next architecture and
现在开始与Facebook正在使用的下一个架构相似
this is now starting to resemble what
Facebook is using the next architecture
仍然需要用户，我们仍然有一堆运行Web服务器的前端服务器
still need users we still have a bunch
of front end servers running web servers
在PHP中，到目前为止，也许还有大量的前端服务器，
in PHP and by now maybe a vast number of
front end servers we still have our
数据库服务器，因为您知道我们需要一个可以存储数据的系统
database servers because you know we
need us a system that will store data
为我们安全地存储在磁盘上，我们将为我们提供诸如交易之类的信息
safely on disk for us and we'll provide
things like transactions for us and so
你知道可能想要一个数据库，但是在这两者之间
you know probably want a database for
that but in between we're gonna have a
缓存层就是memcache D进入的地方
caching layer that's this is where
memcache D comes in
当然还有其他可以使用的内容，但memcache
and of course there's other things you
could use that the memcache but memcache
D碰巧是一种非常流行的缓存方案，现在的想法是
D happens to be an extremely popular
caching scheme the idea now is you have
一大堆这些Memcache服务器，以及前端需要读取一些内容时
a whole bunch of these memcache servers
and when a front-end needs to read some
数据首先要做的是询问其中一个Memcache服务器，看您是否拥有
data the first thing it does is ask one
of the memcache servers look do you have
我需要的数据，它将与一些数据一起发送获取请求
the data I need
so it'll send a get request with some
到其中一个Memcache服务器的密钥，Memcache服务器将检查它是否已获得
key to one of the memcache servers and
the memcache server will check it's got
只是内存中的一个表，实际上memcache非常简单，远
just a table in memory it's in fact
memcache is extremely simple it's far
例如，它远比您的实验室3简单得多，但在
far simpler than your lab 3 for example
it just has just as a big hash table on
它使用哈希表中的键检查它是否返回的内存
memory it checks with that keys in the
hash table if it is it sends back the
数据说，是的，这是我兑现的价值，如果我们
data saying oh yeah here's the value
I've cashed for that and if we if the
在此Memcache服务器中的前端命中率很高，然后我可以生成该网页
front end hits in this memcache server
great I can then produce the webpage
如果前端服务器必须在网络服务器中丢失数据，则在其中添加数据
with that data in it if it misses in the
webserver though the front-end has to
然后后方无关的马术数据库服务器，数据库服务器会说
then rear equesticle irrelevant database
server and the database server will say
哦，您知道这是您需要的数据，这时为了
oh you know here's the here's the data
you need and at that point in order to
兑现用于需要它的下一个前端，我们将发送看跌期权
cash it in for the next front-end that
needs it the front end we'll send a put
将数据与数据库一起存储到该Memcache服务器中，因为
with the data it fashion the database
into that memcache server and because
memcache的运行速度至少提高了10倍，也许快了10倍以上
memcache runs at least 10 and maybe
maybe more than 10 times faster for
对于给定的硬件数量，它确实比数据库具有优势
weeds than the database for a given
amount of hardware it really pays off to
对内存缓存和数据库使用相当数量的某些硬件
use a fair amount some of that hardware
for memcache as well as for the database
服务器，所以人们经常使用这种安排，这只会节省它们
servers so people people use this
arrangement a lot and it just saves them
钱是因为内存缓存对于杂草来说要比数据库服务器快得多
money because memcache is so much faster
for weeds than a database server still
需要向数据库发送写操作，因为您希望有权更新
need to send writes to the database
because you want right to an updates to
持久存储在数据库中，因为如果存在
be stored durably on the database as
this can still be there if there's a
崩溃或其他问题，但是您可以将Reese发送到缓存中的次数更多
crash or something but you can send the
Reese to the cache very much more
很快好了，所以我们有一个问题，问题是为什么内存缓存不会
quickly ok so we have a question the
question is why wouldn't the memcache
服务器实际上代表前端命中了put并缓存了响应
server actually hit the put on behalf of
the front-end and cache the response
在响应前端之前，这是一个很好的问题
before responding the front-end so
that's a great question
您可以想象一个缓存层，您将向其发送获取信息，它将
you could imagine a caching layer that
you would send a get to it and it would
如果它错过了memcache层，则会将请求转发给
if it missed the memcache layer would
would forward the request to the
数据库婴儿响应memcache memcache会将数据添加到其
database babies respond the memcache
memcache would add the data to its
表，然后响应，其原因是内存缓存就像一个
tables and then respond and the reason
for this is that memcache is like a
完全不知道的完全独立的软件
completely separate piece of software
that it doesn't know anything about
数据库，实际上甚至不必使用和组合
databases and it's actually not even
necessarily used and combined in
与数据库结合，尽管通常如此，所以我们无法烘烤
conjunction with the database although
it often is so we can't bake in
将数据库存储到内存缓存中的知识以及更深层次的原因是
knowledge of the database into memcache
and sort of deeper reason is that the
前端通常不是真正地在内存缓存中一对一存储数据库记录
front ends are often not really storing
one for one database records in memcache
几乎总是或非常频繁发生的事情是前端
almost always or very frequently what's
going on is that the front-end will
向数据库发出一些请求，然后以某种方式处理结果
issue some requests to the database and
then process the results somewhat you
知道也许要采取一些步骤将其转换为HTML或将其收集在一起
know maybe take a few steps to turning
it into HTML or sort of collect together
您知道数据库中多行上的多个职业的结果，
you know results from multiple careers
on multiple rows in the database and
将部分处理的信息缓存在内存缓存中
cached partially processed information
in memcache
只是为了避免下一个阅读器不必进行相同的处理，为此
just to save the next reader from having
to do the same processing and for that
原因Memcache并不真正不了解之间的关系
reason memcache it doesn't really does
not understand the relationship between
朋友希望看到的内容是缓存的，以及您如何使用这些数据
what the friends would like to see see
cached and how did you ride that data
从数据库中得知，知识实际上仅在前端的PHP代码中
from the database that knowledge is
really only in the PHP code on the front
因此，即使我们可以构筑一个好主意，我们也无法拥有
end so therefore even though we could be
architectural a good idea we can't have
这种整合是memcache和
this integration here sort of direct
contact between memcache and the
数据库，尽管它可能使缓存一致性的故事变得更多
database although it might make the
cache consistency story much more
直截了当，是的，就是这样，然后回答下一个
straightforward and yes
this is it's this and answer the next
问题是备用现金和现金透视之间的区别
question that is the difference between
a lookaside cash and a look through cash
后备业务的事实是，前端看起来
the fact the lookaside business is that
the front end sort of looks asides to
现金以查看数据是否存在，是否存在数据
the cash to see if the data is there and
if it's not it makes its own
安排让您事半功倍的经历，您可以通过现金了解一下
arrangements for getting the deed on
amiss you know a look through cash my
转发数据库的请求并直接处理并立即处理响应
forward request of the database and
directly and handle the response now
Memcache受欢迎的部分原因是它是后备
part of the reason for the popularity in
memcache is that it is it is a lookaside
现金对于是否存在数据库或存有什么是完全中立的
cash that is completely neutral about
whether there's a database or what's in
数据库或内存缓存中的内容与最终内容之间的关系
the database or the relationship between
stuff in memcache and what's in the end
数据库中的项目都可以，所以这是非常流行的安排
items in the database all right so this
is very popular arrangement very widely
使用它具有成本效益，因为memcache在
used it's cost effective because
memcache is so much faster in the
数据库，每个网站都会使您变得很认真，因此有点复杂
database it's a bit complex every
website that makes serious you so this
面临的问题是，如果您不执行任何操作，则存储在
faces the problem that if you don't do
something the data that's stored in the
缓存将与数据库中的数据不同步，因此每个人
caches will get out of sync with the
data in the database and so everybody
必须有一个故事，说明如何确保在您修改
has to have a story for how to make sure
that when you modify something in the
数据库，您可以对内存缓存执行某些操作，请注意以下事实：
database you do something to memcache to
you know take care of the fact that
然后，内存缓存可能会存储不反映更新的过时数据，并且
memcache may then be storing stale data
that doesn't reflect the updates and a
尽管有其他人，但本文中有很多关于Facebook的故事是什么
lot of this papers about what Facebook
story is for that although other people
有其他计划，这种安排也可能会有点脆弱，它允许您
had other plans this arrangements also
potentially a bit fragile it allows you
扩展到更多的用户，那么您本可以只使用数据库
to scale up to far more users then you
could have gone with databases alone
因为内存缓存是如此之快，但这意味着您将要结束
because memcache is so fast but what
that means is that you're gonna end up
系统承受的负载要高得多，您知道
with the system that's sustaining a load
that's far far higher you know orders of
数量级高于数据库可以处理的数量，因此，如果发生任何事情
magnitude higher than what the databases
could handle and thus if anything goes
例如，如果您的一台内存缓存服务器发生故障，并且
wrong for example if one of your
memcache servers were to fail and
意味着前端现在必须联系数据库，因为
meaning that the front ends would now
have to contact the database because
他们没有击中，他们不能使用它来存储数据
they didn't hit they couldn't use this
to store data
您将大大增加数据库的负载，因为
you're gonna be increasing a load in the
databases dramatically right because
您知道内存缓存的命中率为99％还是
memcache do you know supposing it has a
you know hit rate of 99 percent or
无论碰巧是什么，您都知道Memcache将几乎吸收
whatever it happens to be you know
memcache is gonna be absorbing almost
所有读取数据库后端的操作只会看到百分之几的
all the reads the database backends only
going to be seeing a few percent of the
读取总数，因此这里的任何失败都会增加读取的百分之几
total reads so any failure here is gonna
increase that few percent of the reads
也许您知道我不知道50％的读数或其他
to maybe you know I don't know 50
percent of the reads or whatever which
是一个巨大的数量级增加，就像Facebook一旦完成
is a huge huge order of magnitude
increase so as Facebook does once you've
必须依靠此缓存层，因此您需要认真设置
got to rely on this caching layer you
need to be set up pretty serious
措施，以确保您永远不会暴露数据库层的全部内容
measures to make sure that you never
expose the database layer to the full
像缓存层看到的满负荷之类的东西，您知道
anything like the full load that the
caching layer is seeing and you know you
在Facebook上看到他们有很多想法来确保
see in facebook they have quite a bit of
thought put into making sure the
数据库再也看不到满负荷了
databases don't ever see anything like
the full load okay
到目前为止，这是通用的，我现在想切换到什么
so far this is generic now I want to
sort of switch to a big picture of what
Facebook在论文中描述了它们的整体架构
Facebook describes in the paper for
their overall architecture of course
他们有很多用户，每个用户都是无友，状态和帖子以及
they have lots of users every user as a
friendless and status and posts and
喜欢和喜欢的照片，但Facebook非常容易或试图将数据显示给
likes and photos but Facebook's very
easy or e nted towards showing data to
用户，其中最重要的一点是，新数据不是
users and a super important aspect of
that is that fresh data is not
在这种情况下，您绝对认为应该读
absolutely necessary in that
circumstance you know suppose the reads
您是否知道由于缓存而需要读取几秒钟的产量数据
are you know due to caching supposed to
reads yield data that's a few seconds
过时的数据，因此您要向用户显示的不是最新数据，而是
out of date so you're showing your users
data not the very latest data but the
几秒钟前的数据，您知道用户极不可能
data from a few seconds ago you know
what the users are extremely unlikely to
注意，除非在特殊情况下，否则如果我正在查看今天的新闻提要
notice except in special cases right if
I'm looking at a news feed of today's
你知道今天的新闻你知道我是否从几个新闻中看到
you know today's news you know if I see
the news from a few
以前与现在的新闻相比，没有人会注意到没有人
times ago versus the news from now a big
deal nobody's gonna notice nobody's
会抱怨你知道，并非所有数据都适用，但很多情况下
gonna complain you know that's not
always true for all data but for a lot a
他们必须处理的许多数据都是最新的
lot of the data that they have to deal
with sort of super up-to-date
像线性化能力意义上的一致性实际上不是
consistency in the sense of like
linearise ability is not actually
重要的是重要的是您不会无限期地缓存过时的数据
important what is important is that you
don't cache stale data indefinitely you
知道他们做不到的是错误地拥有了一些正在显示的数据
know what they can't do is by mistake
have some data that they're showing
昨天，上周甚至一个小时前的用户
users that's from yesterday or last week
or even an hour ago those users really
会开始注意到，所以他们不在乎一致性，例如
will start to notice that so they don't
care about consistency like
一秒一秒，但他们很在乎不在不在不能咀嚼
second-by-second but they care a lot
about not not being in cannot chewing
过时的数据来自不止一阵子
stale data from more than well more than
a little while ago the other situation
他们需要提供一致性的是用户是否更新了他们的
in which they need to provide
consistency is if a user updates their
拥有数据，或者用户更新几乎所有数据，然后读取与
own data or if a user updates almost any
data and then reads that same data that
人类知道他们只是更新了，这给用户带来极大的困惑
the human knows that they just updated
it's extremely confusing for the user to
查看过时的数据（如果他们知道他们刚刚进行了更改），因此在特定情况下
see stale data if they know they just
changed it and so in that specific case
Facebook的设计还应谨慎确保用户是否更改了数据
the Facebook design is also careful to
make sure that if a user changes data
该用户将看到更改数据
that that user will see the change data
好的，所以Facebook有多个数据中心，他们称其为区域，我认为
ok so Facebook has multiple data centers
which they call regions and I think at
在撰写本文时，他们有两个区域是主要区域
the time this paper was written they had
two regions their sort of primary region
在加利福尼亚的西海岸，他们的次要地区在
was on the west coast California and
their sort of secondary region was in
东海岸和两个数据中心看起来非常相似
the East Coast and the two data centers
look pretty similar you
运行我的续集的数据库服务器集
set of database servers running my
sequel the sharted date over these my
续集数据库服务器
sequel database servers
他们有一堆memcache D服务器，我们将看到它们实际上是
they had a bunch of memcache D servers
which we'll see they are actually
排列成独立的集群，然后它们有一堆前端
arranged in independent clusters and
then they had a bunch of front ends
在每个数据中心中又有一个单独的安排，有几个
again sort of a separate arrangement in
each data center and there's a couple
造成这种情况的原因是，他们的客户分散在各地
reasons for this one is that their
customers were scattered all over the
国家，这对于东方人的表演是一件好事
country and it's nice just for a
performance that people on the East
海岸可以与附近的数据中心对话，西海岸的人也可以
Coast can talk to a nearby data center
and people on the west coast can also
与附近的赤字交谈只会使互联网延迟现在减少
talk to a nearby deficit it just makes
internet delays less now the the data
中心不对称，每个中心都拥有所有数据的完整副本
centers were not symmetric each of them
held a complete copy of all the data
他们没有将数据分片到整个数据中心，所以西方
they didn't sort of shard the data
across the data centers so the West
我认为Coast是主要的，它具有数据的真实副本和
Coast I think was a primary and it sort
of had the real copy of the data and the
东海岸是次要的，真正的意思是所有权利都必须
East Coast was a secondary and what that
really means is that all rights had to
被发送到相关数据库，而第一天将成为中心，因此您知道
be sent to the relevant database and the
primary day to be Center so you know any
正确发送给您，您在这里知道，他们使用他们服务的我的续集的功能
right gets sent you know here and they
use a feature of my sequel they serve
异步日志复制方案，以使每个数据库都位于主区域中
asynchronous log replication scheme to
have each database in the primary region
将每个更新发送到辅助区域中的相应数据库，以便
send every update to the corresponding
database in secondary region so that
这些数据库服务器可能会有几秒钟的延迟
with a lag of maybe even a few seconds
these database servers would have
相同的内容，辅助数据库服务器将具有与以下内容相同的内容
identical content the secondary database
servers would have identical content to
小学读尽管我们是本地的，所以这些前端在他们需要
the primaries reads though we're local
so these front ends when they need to
找到一些我通常会与该数据中心内的memcache memcache对话的数据
find some data I'm in general would talk
to memcache memcache in that data center
如果他们错过了内存缓存，那么他们会与他们从
and if they missed in memcache they
talked to the they'd read from the
在同一数据数据中心再次建立数据库
database in that same data data center
um again though the databases are
在这两个区域中的这两个区域上完整复制所有数据
complete replicas all the data's on both
of these these in both of these regions
这是整体情况，我接下来要谈的是几件事
that's the overall picture the next
thing I want to talk about is a few
有关如何使用它们的详细信息，您知道这种白细胞缓存
details about how they how they use you
know with this leukocyte caching
实际上看起来像这样，确实有读写功能，这是
actually looks like so there's really
there's reads and writes and this is
读图二所示
just what's shown in Figure two for a
read
如果您读取任何数据，那么在前端执行的第一件事
which is executing on a front-end the
first thing if you read any data that
可能会缓存前端代码的第一件事是
might be cached the first thing that
code in the front-end does is makes this
使用所需数据的键进行库调用，并生成一个
get library call with the key of the
data they want and get just generates an
RPC到相关的Memcache服务器，因此他们在该库例程哈希值上哈希
RPC to the relevant memcache server so
they hash this library routine hashes on
客户端通过哈希键选择内存缓存服务器，然后向该服务器发送RPC
the client hashes the key to pick the
memcache server and sends an RPC to that
mcat服务器，他们随随便便回答是的，这是您的数据，或者也许它将指向
mcat server them casually reply yes
here's your data or or maybe it'll point
nil表示我没有该数据，因此不进行缓存，因此如果V为nil，则
nil saying I don't have that data it's
not cached so if if V is nil then the
前端将发出从中获取数据所需的任何续集查询
front-end will issue whatever sequel
query is required to fetch the data from
数据库，然后进行另一个RPC调用
the database and then make another RPC
call
-memk2相关的memcache服务器以将获取数据安装在memcache中
- memk2 the relevant memcache server to
install the fetch data in the memcache
服务器，所以这只是我之前讨论过的例程
server so this is just the routine I
talked through before
这就是后备缓存的作用，正确的
it's kind of what lookaside caching does
and for right
你知道V是写作，我们有一个键和一个值，没有林蛙权利，所以图书馆
you know V is the writing we have a key
and a value no Rana right and so library
每个前端的例程，我们将把新数据发送到数据库
routine on an each front end we're gonna
send the the new data to the database
而且您知道我在Keene之前提到的价值可能会有点
and you know I as I mentioned before the
Keene the value may be a little bit
不同，您知道数据库中存储的内容通常在某种程度上
different you know what's stored in the
database is often in a somewhat
与存储在内存缓存中的形式不同，请看一下，但我们现在可以想象
different form from what's stored in
memcache see but we'll imagine for now
相同，一旦数据库具有新数据，则正确的库例程
the same and once the database has the
new data then the right library routine
发送RPC到memcache，详细说明它看起来像您必须删除此键，所以我
sends an RPC to memcache detailing it
look you got to delete this key so I
想要写作者使内存缓存中的密钥无效吗？
want to write the writer is invalidating
the key in memcache do you know what
这意味着下一个尝试从中读取该密钥的前端
that means is that the next front-end
that tries to read that key from
memcache D将会归零，因为它不再被缓存并且将获取
memcache D is gonna get nil back because
it's no longer cached and will fetch the
更新数据库中的值并将其安装到内存缓存中，这样
updated value from the database and
install it into memcache all right so
特别是这是无效的，不是您无法想象一个方案
this is an invalidation in particular
it's not you could imagine a scheme that
会在此时将新数据发送到memcache T，但实际上并没有
would send the new data to memcache T at
this point but it doesn't actually do
这而不是gliese它，实际上在facebook计划的上下文中
that instead of gliese it and actually
in the context of facebook scheme the
需要删除的真正原因是
real reason why this delete is needed is
so that
我们将看到他们的权利，因为实际上在他们的计划中，记忆猫是我的
we'll see their own rights because in
fact in their scheme the mem cat the my
续集服务器数据库服务器也发送删除您和前台之一
sequel server the database servers also
send deletes one of you and the front
端使用混合尖叫机制在数据库中写一些东西
end writes something in the database the
database with the mix squeal mechanism
该论文提到将相关删除内容发送到内存缓存服务器
the paper mentions well send the
relevant deletes to the memcache servers
可能拥有此键的数据，因此数据库服务器将实际
that that might hold this key so the
data the database servers will actually
逐步使内存缓存中的内容失效可能会花费一些时间，但是因为
invalidate stuff in memcache by-and-bye
may take them a while um but because
可能要花一些时间才能删除前端的密钥
that might take a while the front ends
also delete the key said that a front
端不会看到刚刚更新的数据的过时值
end won't see a stale value for data
that it just updated okay
这几乎是每个人都使用memcache的背景
all sort of the background of this is
pretty much how everybody uses memcache
G现在这里还没有什么特别特别的东西，最终您知道了
G there's nothing yet really very
special here now eventually you know the
纸上的所有内容都是关于解决一致性问题的，
paper is all about on the surface all
about solving consistency problems and
确实，这些很重要，但是它们之所以会遇到的原因
indeed those are important but the
reason why they got where they ran into
这些一致性问题主要是因为您知道他们修改了
those consistency problems is in large
part because they you know modify the
设计或建立具有极高性能的设计，因为它们
design or set up a design that had
extremely high performance because they
有极高的负载，并说他们迫切希望获得性能，
had extremely high load and say they
were desperate to get performance and
为了改善性能而进行了一些努力
kind of struggled along behind the
performance improvements in order to
保持合理的一致性水平，并且因为性能来了
retain a reasonable level of consistency
and because the performance kind of came
首先对他们来说，我实际上要谈论
first for them I'm actually going to
talk about
他们的绩效架构，然后再讨论如何解决
their performance architecture before
talking about how they fix the
一致性好不好意思，这里有很多问题我还没有
consistency okay sorry there's been a
bunch of questions here that I haven't
看到让我偷看好吧，一个问题，这意味着复制
seen let me take a peek okay so one
question this means that the replicated
从主要我的续集数据库到次要数据库的更新也必须
updates from the primary my sequel
database to the secondary must also
问题已删除-是的，所以我认为这是对以前版本的引用或
issue deletes - yeah so this is I think
a reference to the previous or
架构幻灯片观察到的是，确实是当前端发送一个
architecture slide the observation is
that yes indeed when a front-end sends a
今天写入数据库服务器，每个服务器都会更新其磁盘上的数据，
write to the database server today every
server updates its data on disk and it
会将无效删除信息发送到其中的任何Memcache服务器
will send an invalidate a delete to
whatever memcache server there is in the
本地区域可能具有仅密钥的本地数据中心
local region the local data center that
might have had the key that was just
更新后，数据库服务器还会将更新的一种表示形式发送到
updated the database server also sends a
sort of representation of the update to
相应的数据库在其应用的其他区域中服务
the corresponding database serve in the
other region which process it applies
磁盘上磁盘数据的权利还可以使用它们原谅
the right to its disk data on disk it
also using them excuse sort of log
读取设备找出哪个内存缓存服务器可能持有该密钥
reading apparatus figures out which
memcache server might hold the key that
刚刚更新，并将其删除也发送到该Memcache服务器，以便
was just updated and sends it delete
also to that memcache server so that the
如果是关键，则在两个数据中心中的缓存均无效，所以另一个
if it's the key is cache is invalidated
in in both data centers okay so another
问题，如果我们先在右侧删除然后发送到
question what would happen if we delete
first in the right and then send to the
数据库
database
因此，如果我们对
so that's or with reference to this
thing here would what if we did to the
首先，如果您确实要删除，那么您会增加机会
feet first you know if you do delete
first then you're increasing the chances
其他一些客户端（假设您删除了该客户端，然后将其发送到数据库）
that some other clients so supposing you
delete and then send to database right
在这里，如果另一个客户读到相同的密钥，他们会在这里错过
in here if another client reads that
same key they're gonna miss at this
他们将要从数据库中获取旧数据，然后
point they're gonna fetch the old data
from the database and they're gonna then
插入现金，然后您将对其进行更新
insert it
cash and then you're going to update it
至少将过时的数据与Memcache保持一会儿，然后如果这
leaving memcache for a while at least
with stale data and then if this the
编写客户端再次读取它，即使它只是
writing client reads it again it may see
the stale data even though it just
更新它进行第二次删除，您知道这些可能性
updated it doing the delete second um
you know these over the possibility that
有人会在这段时间内阅读并看到窃取数据，但他们没有
somebody will read during this period of
time and see steal data but they're not
总的来说，他们担心过时的数据，他们真的最担心
worried about stale data in general
they're really most worried in this
关于客户阅读自己的权利的上下文，因此即使存在
context about clients reading their own
rights so on balance even though there's
我执行删除操作时出现的一致性问题可确保
a consistency problem by the way I'm
doing the delete second ensures that
无论哪种情况，客户最终都将拥有自己的权利，最终数据库
clients will be their own rights in
either case eventually the database
我刚才提到的服务器将发送删除的书面密钥
server as I'm just mentioned will send a
delete for the written keys
我对如何编写新值显示过时的数据感到困惑的另一个问题
another question I'm confused on how
writing the new value shows stale data
但是删除并不能让我看到我不确定该问题在问什么
but deleting doesn't let me see I'm not
really sure what the question is asking
如果它是参考此代码的，一旦写入完成就可以了
the if it's with reference to this code
once the writes done okay maybe the
问题是，实际上我们根本没有删除，因此当客户
question is it's really we didn't do
delete at all so that when a client a
前端网络做了一个或想要更新他David只会告诉
front web for an end did or wanted to
update him David would just tell the
数据库，但未从memcache显式删除数据
database but not explicitly delete the
data from memcache the problem with this
就是如果客户端将此写入发送到数据库，然后立即读取
is that if the client sent this write to
the database and then immediately read
读取的相同数据将从memcache中输出，因为memcache
the same data that read would come out
of the memcache and because memcache
仍然有旧数据，您知道内存缓存尚未正确显示
still has the old data
you know memcache hasn't seen this right
客户端更新了一些数据，然后读取它，您知道在
yet a client that updated some data and
then read it you know updates it in the
数据库，但如果过时的数据是从memcache中读取的，则它将读取数据，然后
database but it reads the data if the
stale data from memcache and then a
客户端可能会更新一些数据，但仍会看到旧数据，如果您将其删除，
client might update some data but still
see the old data and if you delete it
从memcache中删除，那么如果您这样做的话，那么一个客户端要比写入的客户端
from memcache then if a client if you do
do this delete than a client that writes
一些数据，并将其从内存缓存中删除，然后再次读取，它将丢失
some data and deletes it from memcache
and then reads it again it'll miss in
内存缓存是因为删除而不必去数据库
memcache because of the delete and they
don't have to go to the database and
读取数据，数据库将为它提供新鲜的数据，所以问题是
read the data and the database will give
it fresh data okay so the question is
为什么我们为什么要在这里删除天哪，为什么我们不只是这个呢
how come why do we delete here
gosh why don't we just instead of this
直接删除客户端，因为它知道新数据就发送一个
delete have the client just directly
since it knows the new data just send a
设置RPC-memcache T，这是一个好问题
set RPC - memcache T and this is a this
is a good question
所以在这里，我们正在做一个无效方案，这通常是
称为更新方案，让我尝试制作一个示例，该示例显示
called an update scheme and let me try
to cook up an example that shows that
虽然可以使它适用于此更新方案，但它不起作用
while this could probably be made to
work this update scheme it doesn't work
它开箱即用，您不需要小心
it doesn't work out of the box and you
wouldn't you need to do some careful
为了使其能够工作而设计，所以现在客户不想要摆姿势
design in order to make it work so this
wasn't client wants posing up now we
有两个客户
have two clients
读和写相同的密钥交错，所以假设客户一个
reading and writing the same key
interleaved so let's say client one
告诉数据库，您知道将X加号发送给数据库
tells the database you know sends X plus
plus to the database right just
递增X，然后当然还是让我说它将从
incrementing X and then of course or let
me say it's going to increment X from
零到一，因此将X设置为一，然后在该客户之后将呼叫
zero to one so set X to one and then
after that client one is going to call
我们的键集X和值1并将其写入内存缓存D
set of our key which is X and the value
one and write that at the memcache D
假设同时客户2也想增加X，所以它将
supposing meanwhile client two also
wants to increment X so it's going to
读取数据库中的最新值，几乎可以肯定，这些实际上是
read this latest value in the database
and almost certainly these are in fact
交易，所以如果我们要增加客户该怎么办？
transactions so what if we were doing
increment what client won't won't be
发送将是数据库上某种增量交易，用于
sending would be some sort of increment
transaction on the database for
正确性，因为该数据库确实支持事务处理，因此我们将
correctness because the database does
support transactions so we're going to
假设客户将x的值递增到，以将该增量发送到
imagine the client to increments the
value of x to to sends that increment to
数据库和客户端两个也将执行此设置，因此它将
the database and client two also is
going to do this set so it's going to
将X设置为2，但现在剩下的是内存缓存D中1的值
set X to be two but now what we're left
with is the value of one in memcache D
即使正确的值和要说的数据库
even though the correct values and the
databases to which is to say if we do
设置了此更新，即使它确实为我们节省了一些时间，因为现在
this update was set even though it does
save us some time right cuz now we're
避免将来有人错过，因为我们直接说而不是
saving somebody a miss in the future
because we directly said instead of
如果它是留下陈旧数据的流行数据，则删除也有风险
delete we also run the risk if the if
it's popular data of leaving stale data
在数据库中不是不是您无法以某种方式使它工作，而是
in the database it's not that you
couldn't get this to work somehow but it
确实需要仔细考虑才能解决此问题，所以这就是为什么
does require some careful thought to fix
this problem all right so that was why
他们使用了invalidate而不是更新，所以我打算
they use invalidate and instead of
update okay so I was going to
关于绩效，他们如何获得绩效的这种途径是
about performance they this sort of
route of how they get performance is
通过并行并行化并行执行并用于存储
through parallel parallelization
parallel execution and for a storage
系统只是一个高层次上，实际上有两种方法可以使您获得良好的
system just at a high level there's
really two ways that you can get a good
性能之一是通过分区进行分片
performance
one is by partition which is sharding
那就是你拿走你的数据，然后把它分成十个部分
that is you take your data and you split
it up over you know into ten pieces over
十台服务器，那十台服务器可以独立运行
ten servers and those ten servers can
run independently hopefully the other
复制时可以使用额外硬件获得更高性能的方法
way you can use extra hardware to get
higher performance despite replication
在拥有一个以上的数据副本，而您对于给定的数量
at is have more than one copy of the
data and you kind of for a given amount
硬件类型，您可以选择是否对数据进行分区或
of hardware you can kind of choose
whether to partition your data or
复制它以使用该硬件，您从中了解到
replicate it in order to use that
hardware and there's you know from
memcache，看看我们在这里谈论的是通过
memcache see what we're talking about
here is is splitting the data over the
通过散列密钥来使用可用的Memcache服务器，从而使每种密钥都能生存
available memcache servers by hashing
the key so that every key sort of lives
在一个内存缓存服务器上，从内存缓存中，我们在这里谈论的是
on one memcache server and from memcache
what we would be talking about here is
让每个前端仅与单个Memcache服务器对话并发送其所有
having each front-end just talk to a
single memcache server and send all its
请求在那里，以便每个内存缓存服务器仅服务前端的一个子集
requests there so that each memcache
server serves only a subset of the front
结束并满足他们的所有需求，Facebook实际上使用了一种组合
ends and sort of serves all their needs
and Facebook actually uses a combination
分区和复制都可以对分区中的事物进行分区
of both partition and replication for
partition the things that are in its
支持一个原因是它的存储效率很高，因为您只存储一个副本
favor one is that it's memory efficient
because you only store a single copy of
复制中的每个项目Abita您将存储每个数据
each item Abita where's in replication
you're gonna store every piece of data
也许在每个分区上的服务器上，只要
maybe on every server on the sort of
partition is that it's as long as your
钥匙在某种程度上同样受欢迎，但是效果很好，但是如果有
keys are sort of equally roughly equally
popular works pretty well but if there's
一些热键，热键分区对您的帮助并不大
some hot a few hot keys partition
doesn't really help you much once you
获得足够的分区，以使这些热键位于不同的服务器上
get those partition enough that those
hot keys are on different servers you
一次知道是否有一个热键，例如没有
know once the if there's a single hot
key for example no amount of
分区可以为您提供帮助，因为无论您对该热键进行多少分区
partitioning helps you because no matter
of how much you partition that hot key
仍然坐在一台服务器上
is still sitting on just one server
问题分区是，这并不意味着前端需要前端
the problem partition is that it doesn't
mean that the front if front ends need
要使用大量不同键的数据，这意味着最后每个前端
to use lots of data lots of different
keys it means in the end each front-end
可能会与许多分区进行通信，至少如果您使用
is probably going to talk to lots of
partitions and at least if you use
像TCP这样的保持状态的协议会给您带来巨大的开销
protocols like TCP that keep state
there's significant overhead to as you
为复制添加越来越多的N平方通信
add more and more sort of N squared
communication for a replication it's
如果您的问题是一些键很受欢迎，那太棒了，因为现在您
fantastic if if your problem is that a
few keys are popular because now you
知道您正在复制这些热键，并且可以为每个热键服务
know you're making replicas of those
those hotkeys and you can serve each
并行复制相同的密钥，这很好，因为它的数量更少
replica the same key in parallel it's
good because there's fewer this there's
每个前端可能只与一个人通话，而不是平方通信
not n squared communication each
front-end maybe only talks to one
内存缓存服务器，但坏的地方是每个服务器中都有一个数据副本
memcache server but the bad thing is
it's there's a copy of data in every
在服务器上，您可以通过复制然后通过以下方式缓存更少的独特数据项
server you can cache far fewer distinct
data items with replication then with
分区，因此可以存储的总数据更少，所以这些只是通用的
partition so there's less total data can
be stored so these are just generic for
这两种使用额外硬件来提高性能的主要方法的利弊
pros and cons of these two main ways of
using extra hardware to get higher
性能还不错，所以我想谈一谈这种情况
performance alright so I want to talk a
bit about there when one sort of context
他们使用分区和复制的级别是不同的
in which they use partition and
replication is at the level of different
地区，所以我只想说说为什么他们决定要
regions so I just want to talk through
why it is that they decided to have
单独的区域和种类完整的数据中心，其中包含所有数据
separate regions and kind of separate
complete data center with all the data
在每个地区，所以在我这样做之前，我有一个问题，为什么我们不能
in each of the regions so I before I do
that there's a question why can't we
可以通过复制缓存相同数量的数据，所以假设您有10个
cache the same amount of data with
replication ok so supposing you have 10
每台计算机都有1 GB的RAM，您可以将这10台计算机分别用于
machines each with a gigabyte of RAM and
you can use these 10 machines each with
一个GB的RAM，用于复制或分区方案（如果您使用
a gigabyte of RAM for either replication
or in a partitioning scheme if you use a
每个服务器存储彼此不同数据的分区方案
partitioning scheme where each server
stores different data from the other
服务器上，您总共可以存储10 GB的不同数据对象
servers that you can store a total of 10
gigabytes of distinct data objects on
您的10台服务器各有1 GB的RAM，因此对于分区，您知道每个字节
your 10 servers each with a gigabyte of
RAM so with partition you know each byte
的ram用于不同的数据，因此您可以查看您的RAM总量
of ram is used for different data so you
can look at the total amount of RAM you
这就是您知道可以存储多少不同数据的不同数据
have that's how much distinct data you
know different data items you can store
通过复制，您知道您的用户或多或少都在关注
with replication you know assuming your
users are more or less looking at the
每个副本每个缓存相同的东西最终将大致存储
same stuff each each replicas each cache
replicas will end up storing roughly the
与所有其他缓存相同的东西，所以您的10个拥有10 GB的RAM
same stuff as all the other caches so
your 10 you have 10 gigabytes of RAM
仍然他们和您的10台机器，但其中每台机器大致存储
still they and your 10 machines but each
of those machines stores roughly the
相同的数据，那么您最终会得到这10个相同千兆字节项目的副本吗？
same data so would you end up with this
10 copies of the same gigabyte of items
因此在这个特定示例中，如果您使用复制，
so in a can this particular example if
you use replication you
打attempt尝试许多不同的数据项，您知道实际上可能是
snoring attempt as many distinct data
items and you know that may actually be
一个好主意取决于您了解数据的某种方式，但它确实
a good idea depending on you know sort
of way your data is like but it does
意味着复制使您缓存的总数据更少，您知道
mean that replication gives you less
total data that's cached and you know
您可以看到纸质字词中提到了这种张力
you can see there's points in the paper
word that they mention this tension
名义上，它们不会落在另一侧，因为它们同时使用
nominally they don't come down on one
side of the other because they use both
复制和制图好吧好吧，所以它们处于最高级别
replication and charting okay okay so
the highest level at which they're
玩此游戏是在区域之间进行的，因此在每个区域的较高级别上
playing this game is between regions and
so it at this high level each region has
所有数据的完整副本，它们具有每个区域的完整信息
a complete replica of all the data right
they have a each region as a complete
数据库服务器集每个数据库数据库对应的数据库服务器
set of database servers each database
database corresponding database servers
对于相同的数据并假设用户正在或多或少地看到相同的东西
for the same data and assuming users are
looking at more or less the same stuff
这意味着不同区域的内存缓存服务器也存储着更多
that means the memcache servers in the
different regions are also storing more
或基本上没有复制，我们在两个地方都复制了您的
or less basically replicating where we
have yours replicating in both the
数据库服务器和内存缓存服务器，还有一点是
database servers and the memcache
servers and the point again one point is
您想要一个完整的网站副本，该副本与
to you want a complete copy of the site
that's close to West Coast users in the
互联网初期的互联网负载和完整网站的另一个副本
internet load early in the internet and
another copy of the complete website
这个靠近东海岸的用户再次关闭了互联网，
this close to users on the East Coast
close on the internet again and the
互联网非常快，但是您知道50毫秒还是
Internet's pretty fast but coast to
coast is you know 50 milliseconds or
如果用户必须等待太多50毫秒，该怎么办
something which if you do if users have
to wait too many 50 millisecond
他们会开始注意到间隔时间的另一个原因是
intervals they'll start to notice that
amount of time another reason is that
您想在两者之间应用数据的理由
the you wanna a reason to
applicate the data between the two
这些前端甚至可以为用户创建一个网页
regions is that these front ends to even
create a single web page for user
通常从缓存中请求数十个或数百个不同的数据项
requests often dozens or hundreds of
distinct data items from the cache or
数据库，因此速度加快了延迟，前端延迟了
the databases and so the speed the
latency the delay at which a front-end
可以从memcache键的外观中获取这数百个项目
can fetch these hundreds of items from
that from the look from the memcache key
非常重要，因此拥有前台
is quite important and so it's extremely
important to have the front and only
交谈只读取本地内存缓存服务器和本地数据库，以便您可以
talk to only read local memcache servers
and local databases so that you can do
它需要非常快速地对网页执行数百个查询，因此如果我们
the hundreds of queries it needs to do
for a web page very rapidly so if we
已经在两个区域之间对数据进行了分区，那么前端您是否知道
have partitioned the data between the
two regions then a front-end you know if
我正在看我的朋友，有些朋友在东海岸，有些在
I'm looking at my friends and some of my
friends are on the East Coast and some
在西海岸，这意味着如果我们进行分区，可能需要
on the west coast that means if we
partitioned that would might require the
前端实际上发出了许多您知道每个50毫秒的请求
front ends to actually make many
requests you know 50 milliseconds each
到另一个数据中心，用户会看到这种延迟，
to the other data center and users would
users would see this kind of latency and
很难过，所以复制的另一个原因是保持
be very upset so so the reason to
another reason to replicate is to keep
前端总是靠近数据，而他们需要的所有数据
the front ends always close to the data
to all the data they need of course this
使写入操作更加昂贵，因为现在如果前端和次要区域
makes writes more expensive because now
if a front-end and the secondary region
需要写estest整个互联网上发送数据的方式
needs to write in estes send the data
all the way across the internet the
读取的频率远远高于正确的读取频率，因此尽管这是一个不错的权衡
reads are far far more frequent than
right so it's a good trade-off although
该论文没有提及可能是另一个原因
the paper doesn't mention it it's
possible that another reason for
两个站点之间的完全复制是这样，如果主站点
complete replication between the two
sites is so that if the primary site
掉下来，也许他们可以将整个操作切换到辅助站点
goes down perhaps they could switch the
whole operation to the secondary site
但我不知道他们是否想到了
but I don't know if they had that in
mind
好的，这是摄政人之间的故事，基本上是
okay so this is the story between
Regents is basically a story of
两个数据中心之间的复制
replication between the two data centers
现在在一个区域内的数据中心内，因此在每个区域内
all right now within a data center
within a region so in each region
只有一组数据库服务器
there's a single set of database servers
因此，在数据库级别，数据被绘制成图表，而不是在每个数据库内部复制
so at the database level the data is
charted and not replicated inside each
但是在内存缓存级别，他们实际上使用复制以及
region however at the memcache level
they actually use replication as well as
绘制图表，因此他们具有聚类的概念，因此实际上是给定区域
charting so they had this notion of
clusters so a given regions actually
支持前端和数据库服务器的多个集群，所以我在这里
supports multiple clusters of front-ends
and database servers so here I'm going
在这个区域有两个集群，这个集群有一个你知道的前面
to have two clusters in this region this
cluster has a you know a bunch of front
末端和一堆内存缓存服务器，它们几乎完全独立
ends and a bunch of memcache servers and
these are completely independent almost
完全独立，因此前端和集群可以发送其所有信息
completely independent so that a
front-end and cluster one sends all its
读取到本地内存缓存服务器，但错过了它需要转到一台
reads to the local memcache servers and
misses it needs to go to the one instead
数据库服务器以及该集群中的每个前端的数量
of database servers and similarly each
front-end in this cluster
只与同一个集群中的Memcache服务器通信，为什么它们具有此功能
talks only to memcache servers in the
same cluster so why do they have this
多个群集为什么不只是本质上知道一个群集
multiple clusters why not just have you
know essentially a single cluster a
共享一组前端服务器和一组内存缓存服务器
single set of front end servers and a
single set of memcache server is shared
所有这些前端之一就是，如果您这样做了，那将意味着您
by all those front ends one is that if
you did that and and that would mean you
知道是否需要扩大容量，您会增加更多
know if you need to scale up capacity
you sort of be adding more and more
前端的Memcache服务器与您无法获得任何胜利的同一群集
memcache servers in front ends to the
same cluster you don't get any win
因此，您可以了解流行键的性能，因此
therefore in performance for popular
Keys you know so there the data sort of
此内存缓存服务是某种混合，您知道大多数可能仅用于
this memcache service is sort of a mix
you know most of it is maybe only used
由少数用户提供，但其中有些东西很多
by a small number of users but there's
some stuff there that lots and lots of
用户需要查看并通过使用复制以及分片来获得
users need to look at and by using
replication as well as sharding they get
您知道非常受欢迎的密钥的多个副本，因此它们得到了排序
you know multiple copies of the very
popular keys and therefore they get sort
这些键在不同群集之间的并行服务
of parallel serving of those keys
between the different clusters another
也不想增加群集大小的原因
reason to not want to increase the size
of the cluster individual cluster too
大部分是集群中的所有数据分布在分区上
much is that all the data within a
cluster is spread over partitioned over
所有的内存缓存服务器和任何一个前端通常实际上都将
all the memcache servers and any one
front end is typically actually going to
最终可能需要从每个内存缓存服务器中获取数据，所以这
need data from probably every single
memcache server eventually and so this
表示您在前端之间有一种n平方的交流模式
means you have a sort of n-squared
communication pattern between the front
终端和内存缓存服务器，并在一定程度上使用了TCP
ends and the memcache servers and to the
extent that they're using TCP for the
涉及大量开销，大量连接的通信
communication that involves a lot of
overhead a lot of sort of connection
状态为所有不同的TCP，所以他们想限制，所以你知道这是N
state for all the different TCP so they
wanted to limit so you know this is N
他们想限制中共的平方，这样做的方法是
squared CCP's they want to limit the
growth of this and the way to do that is
确保没有一个簇变得太大，所以这个N平方不会
to make sure that no one cluster gets to
be too big so this N squared doesn't get
太大了
too large
与此相关的是，他们在种姓拥挤行业中
and well related to that is this in
caste congestion business they're
谈论如果主持人需要来自许多Memcache服务器的数据，
talking about the if a frontman needs
data from lots of memcache servers it's
实际上它将或多或少全部发出请求
actually it's gonna send out the
requests more or less all at the same
时间，这意味着该前端将获得所有
time and that means this front-end is
gonna get the responses from all the
记忆快取伺服器或多或少会在同一时间查询
memcache servers to query it more or
less the same side time and that may
意味着数十或数百个数据包同时全部到达此处
mean dozens or hundreds of packets
arriving here all at the same time which
如果您不小心，将导致种姓拥塞和
if you're not careful we'll cause packet
losses that's in caste congestion and in
为了限制那是多么糟糕，你有他们谈论的一堆技术
order to limit how bad that was that you
had a bunch of techniques they talked
大约一个，但其中一个并没有使群集太大，因此
about but one of them was not making the
clusters too large so that the number of
memcache使前端倾向于与之对话，并且他们可能在做出贡献
memcache has given front-end tend to
talk to and they might be contributing
同一种姓永远不会太大，这也是论文的最终原因
to the same caste never got to be too
large and a final reason the paper
提到的是它的背后或背后是数据中心中的大型网络，
mentions is that it's or behind this is
is a big network in the data center and
很难建立既像每秒许多位又快的网络
it's hard to build networks that are
both fast like many bits per second and
可以与很多不同的计算机通话，并且可以拆分数据
can talk to lots and lots of different
computers and by splitting the data
集中到这些集群中，并使大多数通信持续进行
center up into these clusters and having
most of the communication go on just
在每个集群中，这意味着他们需要较小的，他们需要一个中等的人
within each cluster that means they need
a smaller they need you know a modest
快速设置此群集的网络，并且您知道的适度大小也相当快
size fast Network for this cluster and a
modest size you know reasonably fast
该群集的网络，但他们不必建立一个可以
network for this cluster but they don't
have to build a single network that can
可以处理所有计算机之间的所有流量
sort of handle all of the traffic
between among all the computers of the
巨型集群，因此它限制了基础网络的昂贵程度
giant cluster so it limits how expensive
underlying network is on the other hand
当然，他们正在复制数据和两个群集，并复制那些
of course they're replicating the data
and the two clusters and for items that
不是很受欢迎，也不会从性能中真正受益
aren't very popular and aren't really
going to benefit from the performance
拥有多份副本的胜利，这会浪费在所有RAM上，而您
win of having multiple copies this it's
wasteful to sit on all this RAM and you
知道我们在谈论数百或数千台服务器，因此
know we're talking about hundreds or
thousands of servers so the amount of
他们花在RAM上用于内存缓存服务的钱不是开玩笑，所以除了
money they spent on RAM for the memcache
services is no joke so in addition to
每个群集中的Memcache服务器池还有一个区域池
the pool of memcache servers inside each
cluster there's also this regional pool
区域中所有群集共享的内存缓存服务器的数量
of memcache servers that's
shared by all the clusters in a region
然后进入该区域池，然后在前端修改软件，以便
and into this regional pool they then
modify the software on the front end so
前端软件知道啊
that the software on the front end knows
aha
这个钥匙这个滑雪板的数据实际上并不经常使用而不是存储它
this key the data for this skis actually
not use that often instead of storing it
在我自己的集群的Memcache服务器上，我将存储这个不是很受欢迎的密钥
on a memcache server my own cluster I'm
going to store this not very popular key
在区域池的相应Memcache服务器中，所以这是
in the appropriate memcache server of
the regional pool so this is
区域池，这只是一些数据不是
the regional pool and this is just sort
of an admission that some data is not
受欢迎到足以拥有很多复制品，他们可以通过
popular enough to want to have lots of
replicas of it they can save money by
只能兑现一份副本，这样他们就可以得到这种
only cashing a single copy all right so
that's how they get that's this kind of
他们在每个内部使用的Carol复制与分区策略
Carol replication versus partitioning
strategy they use inside each inside
他们讨论的每个地区都有一个困难，就是他们想
each region a difficulty they had that
they discuss is that when they want to
在数据中心中创建一个新集群，它们实际上具有某种临时性
create a new cluster in a data center
they actually have a sort of temporary
性能问题，因为他们正在使群集运行，所以您知道
performance problem as they're getting
that cluster going so you know supposing
他们决定安装您知道的几百台机器成为新集群
they decide to install you know couple
hundred machines to be a new cluster
与前端新前端新的内存缓存错误，然后将其启动
with the front end new front ends new
memcache errors and then they fire it up
而且您可能会导致一半的用户开始使用新集群
and you know maybe cause half the users
to start using the new cluster I'm gonna
一开始必须很好地使用旧集群
have to use the old cluster well in the
beginning there's nothing in these
内存缓存服务器和所有前端服务器都将在内存缓存中丢失
memcache servers and all the front end
servers are gonna miss on the memcache
服务器，并且至少要从头开始直到
servers and have to go to the databases
and at least at the beginning until
这些记忆快取服务会填入所有
these memcache service gets populated
with all the sort of data that's used a
很多这会绝对增加数据库服务器上的负载
lot this is gonna increase the load on
the database servers absolutely enormous
飞跃是因为在我们添加新集群之前，也许只有数据库服务器
leap because before we added the new
clusters maybe the database servers only
看到了百分之一的读取，因为也许这些内存缓存服务器受到了打击
saw one percent of the reads because
maybe these memcache servers have a hit
比如说99％的阅读率仅意味着
rate of say 99 percent for reads the
only one percent of all that means go to
如果我们添加新集群，则在添加新集群之前，数据库服务器
the database servers before we added the
new cluster if we add a new cluster with
内存缓存服务器中没有任何内容，并将一半的流量发送给它，它将获得
nothing in the memcache servers and send
half the traffic to it it's gonna get a
最初的百分百未命中率正确，所以这意味着您知道我们
hundred percent miss rate initially
right and so that'll mean you know we
消失了，因此总体未命中写入现在将为50％，所以我们走了
gone from and so the overall miss write
will now be 50 percent so we've gone
从这些数据库服务器中为读取的百分之一提供服务，而这些服务器则为50
from these database servers serving one
percent of the reads to them serving 50
阅读次数的百分比，因此至少在这个虚构的示例中，
percent of the reads so at least in this
imaginary example we've been quite
启动这个新集群，我们可能会将数据库的负载增加一个
firing up this new cluster we may
increase the load on the databases by a
系数是50，数据库服务器可能正在运行
factor of 50 and chances are the
database servers were running you know
合理的海岸的能力，当然不是50/50
reasonably Coast's the capacity and
certainly not a factor of 50/50 under
能力，所以如果他们只是这将是世界的绝对终结
capacity and so this would be the
absolute end of the world if they just
像这样启动了一个新集群，所以他们有了这个冷启动想法
fired up a new cluster like that and so
instead they have this cold start idea
在这个新集群中，某处用某种标记来标记该集群
in which a new cluster is sort of marked
by some flag somewhere as being in this
冷启动状态，在这种情况下，前端和新群集
cold start state and in that situation
when a front end and the new cluster
首先错过了它首先拥有的本地内存缓存
misses that actually first first it has
its own local memcache if that says no I
没有数据，那么前端我们将询问相应的内存缓存
don't have the data then the front end
we'll ask the corresponding memcache in
一些暖群集中的另一个群集，该群集已经具有该数据的数据
another cluster in some warm cluster
that already has the data for the data
如果它是流行的数据机会，它将被缓存到我的朋友那里，并将得到它
if it's popular data chances are it'll
be cached my friend and will get its
数据，然后将其安装在本地内存缓存中
data and then it will install it in the
local memcache and it's only if both
本地内存缓存和热内存缓存没有前面的数据
local memcache and the warm memcache
don't have the data that this is front
结束，新集群将从数据库服务器读取，就这样
end and the new cluster will read from
the database servers and so this is it
所以他们在这种冷模式下运行了一段时间
and so they run in this kind of cold
mode for a little while the paper I
think提到了几个小时，直到内存缓存服务器源和新的
think mentions a couple hours until the
memcache servers source and the new
群集开始拥有所有流行数据，然后可以将其关闭
clusters start to have all the popular
data and then they can turn off this
冷功能，仅使用本地群集内存缓存就可以了
cold feature and just use the local
cluster memcache alone it's alright
因此，本文讨论的另一个负载问题是是否遇到了
so another another load problem that the
paper talks about if they ran into and
这又是由这种外观缓存引起的负载问题
this is a load problem again deriving
from this kind of look aside caching
策略被称为雷群和情景
strategies is called the thundering herd
and the the scenario
是假设我们有一些数据，有很多Memcache服务器，但是
is that supposing we have some piece of
data there's lotsa memcache servers but
在此Memcache服务器上存储了一些数据
there's some piece of data stored on
this memcache server there's a whole
一堆通常读的很流行的前端
bunch of front ends that are ordinarily
reading that one piece of very popular
数据，因此他们都在不断发送有关该数据的获取请求，
data so they're all sending constantly
sending get requests for that data the
memcache服务器将其存储在缓存中，它会回答他们，您知道他们的memcache
memcache server has it in the cache it
answers them and you know their memcache
服务器每秒可保存约数百万至数百万个请求，因此我们
server is conserve like millions to
million requests per second so we're
做得很好，当然这里还有一些数据库服务器
doing pretty good and of course there's
some database server sitting back here
拥有该数据的真实副本，但我们不会打扰它，因为它是
that has the real copy of that data but
we're not bothering it because it is
很好地缓存，假设有一些前端出现并修改了这个非常流行的
cached well suppose some front-end comes
along and modifies this very popular
数据，因此它将使用新数据向数据库发送写操作，然后
data so it's going to send a write to
the database with the new data and then
它会将删除内容发送到内存缓存服务器，因为这是权限的方式
it's gonna send a delete to the memcache
server because that's the way rights
工作，所以现在我们已经删除了这些非常受欢迎的数据，我们拥有了所有这些
work so now we've just deleted this
extremely popular data we have all these
前端不断发送数据获取信息，他们都会在这里错过一切
front ends constantly sending gets for
that data they're all gonna miss all at
同时他们都想念的同时将读取请求发送给
the same time they're all gonna now
having missed send a read request to the
前端数据库都在同一时间，所以现在这个前端数据库是
front end database all at the same time
and so now this front-end database is
可能同时面对数十或数百个此数据的请求，因此
faced with maybe dozens or hundreds of
simultaneous requests for this data so
这里的洛斯人会很高，尤其令人失望
the Loews here is gonna be pretty high
and it's particularly disappointing
因为我们知道所有这些请求都是针对同一密钥的，所以数据库是
because we know that all these requests
are for the same key so the database is
一遍又一遍地做同样的工作，以最新的书面回应
going to do the same work over and over
again to respond with the latest written
该密钥的副本，直到最终前端解决了安装新密钥的问题
copy of that key until finally the front
ends get around to installing the new
键入memcache，然后人们开始再次点击，所以这是
key in memcache and then people start
hitting again and so this is the
雷鸣伤害了我们真正想要的是一个单身，您知道如果错过了
Thundering hurt what we'd really like is
a single you know if a miss if there's a
正确，线索和未命中发生在内存缓存中，我们希望我们想要的是
right and the leads and a miss happens
in memcache we'd like what we'd like is
对于错过获取数据并安装数据的第一个前端，
the for the first front end that misses
to fetch the data and install it and for
其他前端就像深呼吸，然后等到新数据
the other front ends just like take a
deep breath then wait until the new data
被缓存，这就是他们的设计
is cached and that's
just what their design does if you look
如果使用了与作品不同的叫做Elise的东西
at the if this thing called Elise which
is different from the pieces were used
到，但他们叫Elise，我们再次从场景开始
to but they call Elise and we start from
scratch in the scenario again let's see
所以现在假设我们在第一个前端询问了一个流行的数据
so now suppose we have a popular piece
of data the first front end that asks
对于缺少memcache的数据，Devo将发回错误，说不
for a data that's missing memcache Devo
will send back an error saying oh no I
我的缓存中没有数据，但是它将安装Elise，这有点独特
don't have the data in my cache but it
will install Elise which is a bit unique
编号，它将选择最少的编号安装在表中并发送此租约
number it'll pick a least number install
it in a table and the send this lease
令牌返回到前端，然后进入其他前端并询问
token back to the front end and then
other front ends that come in and ask
对于相同的基思，他们只会得到一个只是被要求等待，你知道一个季度
for the same Keith they'll simply get a
just be asked to wait you know a quarter
快取记忆体D花费一秒或任何合理的时间，因为
of a second or whatever some reasonable
amount of time by the memcache D because
memcache密钥会看到哈哈，我已经为该密钥发布了租约
the memcache key will see a haha I've
already issued the lease for that key
现在至少有一个潜在的V Sparky服务器会注意到
now there's at least potentially a V
Sparky the server will notice it's
已经发出的通知至少可以让这些等待，所以只有一个
already issued at least for the can tell
these ones to wait so only one of the
服务器的猜测Elise然后该服务器在以下情况下从数据库中请求数据
server's guess Elise this server then
asks for the data from the database when
反对回复妈妈，然后发送看跌期权以获取新数据
against the responds back mom
then it sends the put for the new data
用一把钥匙和上帝的价值，最少的证明那是
with a key and the value of God and the
least proved that it was the one who was
允许写数据memcache的人今天在寻找这些东西
allowed to write the data memcache
people looking for these today aha yeah
您是被授予租赁权的人，它实际上会
you are the the person whose lease was
granted and it'll actually do the
和其他的朋友安装，他们被告知等待将重新发布他们的
install by and by these other friends
who are told the wait will reissue their
现在读到它将在那里，所以如果一切顺利，我们所有人都只能得到一个
reads now that it will be there and so
we all if all goes well get just one
请求到数据库，而不是几十或数百，我认为这是
request to the database instead of
dozens or hundreds and I think it's the
租约的意义在于前端是否在尴尬的时刻失败了，
sense in which is the lease is if the
front-end fails at an awkward moment and
实际上没有从数据库请求数据或没有解决它
doesn't actually request the data from
the database or doesn't get around it
安装它memcache D最终memcache D将删除租约cuz
installing it memcache D eventually
memcache D will delete the lease cuz it
超时，下一个要问的前端将获得新的租约，并希望
times out and the next front end to ask
will get a new lease and will hope that
它将与数据库对话并安装新数据，所以他们会回答问题
it will talk to the database and install
new data so yes they answer the question
如果第一个前端出现故障，租约会超时，是的，是的，所以
the lease does up a time out in case the
first front end fails yes yes okay so
这些租约是雷电群问题的解决方案。
these leases are the their solution to
the Thundering Herd problem um another
他们的问题是，如果这些Memcache服务器之一故障最多
problem they have is that if one of
these memcache servers fails the most
您自然会知道，如果内存缓存服务器没有做任何特别的事情，该怎么办
natural you-know-whats if they don't do
anything special if the memcache server
前端失败将发送请求，他们将获得超时和网络
fails the front ends will send a request
they'll get back a timeout and network
会说jeez，您知道我无法与该主机联系，但从未收到回复
will say jeez that you know I couldn't
contact that host never got a response
真正的I BRE软件所做的就是感觉到它
and what the real I BRE
software does is it then sense it
请求数据库，以便如果Memcache服务器发生故障而我们什么也不做
requests the database so if a memcache
server fails and we don't do anything
特殊的数据库现在将直接暴露给所有读取
special the database is now going to be
exposed directly to the reads all of
这些礁石，我赶上服务器West，这是Memcache服务器可能
these reefs and I'm catch server West
serving this is the memcache server may
一直在为您服务，您知道每秒一百万次读取可能意味着
well have been serving you know a
million reads per second that may mean
这样数据库服务器将可以承受每百万次读取
that the database server would be then
exposed to those million reads per
第二，那么现在还远远不够快，无法对付所有这些杂草
second then it's nowhere near fast
enough to deal with all those weeds now
他们在论文中并未真正提及Facebook，但他们确实实现了自动化
Facebook they don't really talk about in
the paper but they do have automated
机器来替换故障的memcache服务器，但是要花一些时间才能
machinery to replace a failed memcache
server but that takes a while to sort of
设置新服务器，新的内存缓存服务器并重定向所有前端
set up a new server a new memcache
server and redirect all the front-end
到新服务器而不是旧服务器，因此在此期间，他们需要一个
to the new server instead of the old
server so in the meantime they need a
一种临时解决方案，这就是这个想法，所以我们说说瓢
sort of temporary solution and that's
this gutter idea so let's say the scoop
是我们有前端，我们拥有一组普通的内存缓存
is that we have our front ends we have
the sort of ordinary set of memcache
伺服器
servers
数据库，其中一个内存缓存服务已失败，我们正在等待
the database the one of the memcache
service has failed we're kind of waiting
直到自动Memcache服务器替换系统替换了此文件
until the automatic memcache server
replacement system replaces this
在此期间，memcache服务器的朋友正在向其发送请求，
memcache server in the meantime
friends are sending requests to it they
得到一种服务器没有响应来自网络的错误，然后有
get a sort of server did not respond
error from the network and then there's
一组很小的装订线服务器
a presumably small set of gutter servers
他们唯一的目的就是要注视他们，他们必须闲置，除非真正的
whose only purpose in life is to eye
they must be idle except when a real
memcache服务器发生故障，并且当前端出现错误并返回时说get
memcache server fails and when the front
end gets an error back saying that get
无法联系内存缓存服务器，它会将相同的请求发送到其中之一
couldn't contact the memcache server
it'll send the same request to one of
装订线服务器，尽管论文没有说我想像前端
the gutter servers and though the paper
doesn't say I imagine that the front end
将再次对密钥进行哈希处理，以选择要与之通信的装订线服务器
will again hash the key in order to
choose which gutter server to talk to
如果装订线服务器具有巨大的价值
and if the gutter server has the value
that's great
否则，前端服务器将与数据库服务器联系以读取
otherwise the front end server will
contact the database server to read the
值，然后将其安装在内存缓存服务器中，以防其他人
value and then install it in the
memcache server in case somebody else
答案要求提供相同的数据，所以这意味着下水道
answer asks for the same data
so while this means down the gutter
服务器将基本上处理其请求，因此它们将是您的理想选择
servers will handle basically handle its
request and so they'll be a miss you
知道由租赁处理的雷霆牧群
know handled by lease leases the
Thundering Herd
他们至少会是我每个项目上都需要通过的小姐
they'll be at least I need a Miss on
each of the items that was a no-fail
memcache服务器，因此数据库服务器中将有一些负载，但是
memcache server so there will be some
load in the database server but then
希望很快，此内存缓存服务器可以让我获取所有侦听的数据
hopefully quickly this memcache server
will I get all the data that's listen
使用并提供良好的服务，然后将被替换，然后
use and provide good service and then by
and by this will be replaced and then
朋友会知道要与其他替换服务器通话，因为
the friends will know to talk to a
different replacement server and because
他们没有，这是今天的问题，我认为他们不会将删除发送给
they don't and this is today's question
I think that they don't send deletes to
这些装订线服务器，因为既然装订线服务器本来可以接管
these gutter servers because since a
gutter server could have taken over for
任何人，甚至可能超过一种普通的内存缓存服务
anyone and maybe more than one of the
ordinary memcache service it could
实际上有缓存任何键的缓存，这意味着并且可能
actually have cache the caching any key
so that would mean that and there may be
您知道有朋友在谈论它，这意味着无论何时前端
you know friends talking to it that
would mean that whenever a front-end
需要它从内存缓存中删除密钥或数据库中的尖叫声发送时
needs it to delete a key from memcache
or when the squeal on the database sends
删除相关内存缓存服务器的任何密钥，是的，您知道
a delete for any key to the relevant
memcache server yeah you know the the
自然的设计是它还会将删除的副本发送给每个
natural design would be that it would
also send a copy of that delete to every
其中一个装订线服务器，以及用于删除数据的前端的装订线服务器
one of the gutter servers and the same
for front ends that are deleting data
他们会从内存缓存存储中删除，但他们也必须离开
they would delete from the memcache
stores but they would also have to leave
可能来自任何MCAD装订线服务器，它将使
potentially from any
MCAD gutter server that would double the
即使在大多数情况下也必须发送的失败数量
amount of defeats that had to be sent
around even though most of the time
这些装订线服务器什么也不做，也不缓存任何东西，它
these gutter servers aren't doing
anything and don't cache anything and it
没关系，因此为了避免所有这些额外的删除，实际上
doesn't matter and so in order to avoid
all these extra deletes they actually
修复装订线服务器，以便它们非常快速地删除密钥，而不是删除
fix the gutter servers so that they
delete Keys very rapidly instead of
挂在他们身上，直到他们被明确删除为止
hanging on to them until they're
explicitly deleted that was answer to
这个问题很好，所以我想一次讨论一下一致性
the question all right so I wanna talk a
bit about consistency all this at a
超高水平，您知道一致性问题是，有很多
super high level you know the
consistency problem is that there's lots
任何给定数据的数据副本的数量，您知道其中有一个副本
of copies of the data for any given
piece of data you know there's a copy in
主数据库在对应的数据库服务器中有一个副本
the primary database there's a copy in
the corresponding database server of
每个次要区域在每个本地集群中都有该密钥的副本
each of the secondary regions there's a
copy of that key in each local cluster
在每个本地群集中的一个Memcache键中，可能存在
in one of the memcache keys in each
local cluster there may be copies of
该密钥和装订线服务器，并且在其中可能有该密钥的副本
that key and the gutter servers and
there may be copies of the key in the
内存缓存服务器和装订线内存缓存服务器位于彼此的其他区域，因此我们拥有
memcache servers and the gutter memcache
servers at each other region so we have
写入时每条数据的大量副本
lots and lots of copies of every piece
of data running around when a write
进来，你知道所有这些副本上都必须有东西
comes in you know the stuff has to
happen on all those copies and
此外，写入可能来自多个来源，而相同的密钥可能是
furthermore the writes may come from
multiple sources the same key may be
由多个前端同时写入，并且该区域可能是
written at the same time by multiple
front ends and this region may be by
朋友和其他地区，也是这种并发和多重
friends and other regions too and so
it's this concurrency and multiple
由于存在多个前端，因此可以复制和分类多个写入源
copies and sort of multiple sources of
writes since there's multiple front ends
这不仅为陈旧的数据创造了很多机会，而且为
it creates a lot of opportunity for not
just for there to be stale data but for
数据过时的数据要长时间留在系统中，所以我想
data stale data to be left in the system
for long periods of time and so I want
我想从某种意义上说明实际上存在哪些问题
to I want to illustrate what are those
problems actually in a sense we've
当有人问为什么前端不这样做时，我已经谈到了这一点
already talked a bit about this when
somebody asked why the front ends don't
更新为什么删除而不是更新，所以这肯定是一个
update why do they delete instead of
updating so that's certainly one
天气的一个实例多个数据源，所以我们有
instance of the kind of weather
multiple sources of data and so we have
强制执行正确的顺序很麻烦，但这是比赛的另一个例子
trouble enforcing correct order but
here's another example of a race an
更新竞赛，如果他们没有做任何事情，将会留下数据
update race that if they hadn't done
something about it would have left data
无限期过时的数据，并且绝对在memcache中
这将与前面的示例类似，所以假设
it's going to be a similar flavor to the
previous example so supposing we have
客户端，他想读取一个密钥，但是memcache说它没有数据
client one he wants to read a key but
memcache says it doesn't have the data
是小姐，所以C人要从数据库中读取数据，然后
it's a Miss so C one's gonna read the
data from from the database and let's
说它可以收回您想要的一些价值
say it gets back some value that you
want
同时，客户要更新此数据，以便它向您发送有关其汇率的信息
meanwhile client to wants to update this
data so it sends you know its rates he
等于v2并将其发送到数据库，然后您知道写入规则
equals v2 and sends that to the database
and then you know the rule for writes
我们看到的写入代码是，我们下一步要做的是将其从
the code for writes that we saw is that
the next thing we do is delete it from
来自memcache dc c2的数据库将要删除
啊，数据库中的密钥哦，这是星期五，您知道它实际上是c2
ah the key from the database oh that's a
Friday you know it was actually c2
真的不知道memcache d中有什么，但是领导总是存在
doesn't really know what's in memcache d
but the leading was ever there is always
安全，因为肯定不会导致过期数据被删除不会导致
她被寂静了Leena um，这就是报纸所声称的那种感觉
her to be stilled Leena um and this is
the sense that the paper claims that
删除是幂等的，说删除对kabhi总是安全的，但是如果您还记得
delete is idempotent said delete it's
always safe to kabhi but if you recall
如果您错过了读操作并从中读取数据的伪代码
the pseudocode for what a read does if
you miss and you read the data from the
您应该将数据库插入到内存缓存中，因此客户端1
database you're supposed to just insert
that data into memcache so client 1 you
知道可能已经很慢了，最后终于解决了发送一组RPC两个内存缓存的问题
know may have been slow and finally gets
around to sending a set RPC two memcache
T，但它读取版本1并读取a，您现在知道什么是旧的过时版本
T but it read version 1 and read a you
know what is now an old outdated version
数据库中的数据，但将其设置为
of the data from the database but it's
going to set that into
将其设置为内存缓存，是的，您知道发生的另一件事是，我们
set this into memcache and yeah you know
one other thing that happened is that we
知道数据库是每当你写一些东西时我就是发送的数据库
know the database is is whenever you
write something I'm database that sends
删除到内存缓存D，所以当然在这一点上数据库也可能
deletes to memcache D so of course maybe
at this point the database will also
已经为k2m种姓发送了删除，所以现在我们转到
have sent a delete
for k2m caste and so now we get to
删除，但这些租约可能已经拥有并不重要
deletes but it doesn't really matter
right these lease may already have
在客户端更新密钥时发生的情况，因此
happened by the time client one gets
around to updating this key and so at
此时，memcache D将无限期地兑现的过时版本
this point indefinitely the memcache D
will be cashing a stale version of of
这些数据，就没有任何机制了，如果系统
this data and there's just no mechanism
anymore or this is them if the system
以这种方式工作，memcache D没有任何机制可以看到
worked in just this way there's no
mechanism for the memcache D to ever see
以获得将要存储和提供过时数据的实际正确值
to ever get the actual correct value
it's gonna store and serve up stale data
永远为K键
for key K forever
他们是因为他们碰到了这一点，而在数据尚可的情况下
and they because they ran into this and
while they're okay with data being
有点过时了，因为数据永远都过时了
somewhat out-of-date they're not okay
with data being out of date forever
因为用户最终会发现他们正在查看古老的数据，因此
because users will eventually notice
that they're seeing ancient data and so
他们必须解决此问题，必须确保不会发生这种情况
they had to solve this they had to make
sure that this scenario didn't happen
他们实际上也通过租赁机制解决了这个问题
they actually solved this this problem
also with the lease mechanism at the
尽管我们为雷霆宝藏描述了相同的租赁机制
same lease mechanism that we describe
for the Thundering hoard although
租赁机制有一个扩展，可以使这项工作正常进行
there's an extension to the lease
mechanism that makes this work so what
发生的情况是，当Memcache向下倾斜时，Miss指示会看到数据
happens is that when memcache descends
back a Miss indication seeing the data
不在缓存中，它将授予租赁，所以我们得到了Miss指示以及
wasn't in the cache it's gonna grant the
lease so we get the Miss indication plus
这个租约基本上只是一个很大的唯一数，而内存缓存服务器是
this lease which is basically just a big
unique number and the memcache server is
会记住此租约与它知道的此密钥之间的关联
gonna remember that the association
between this lease and this key it knows
有人用租约来更新此密钥，新规则是
that somebody out there with a lease to
update this key the new rule is that
当Memcache服务器从另一个客户端或
when the when the memcache server gets a
delete from either another client or
从数据库服务器中，内存缓存服务器将要删除
from the database server the memcache
server is gonna as well as deleting the
项将使此租约失效，因此一旦这些删除出现
item is going to invalidate this lease
so as soon as either these deletes come
假设Elyse首先到达，则内存缓存服务器将相信这一点
in assuming that Elyse arrived first the
memcache server is gonna believe this
从其表中租赁有关此集合的租赁
lease from its table about leases this
set
集合到达内存缓存服务器后，现在是从前端退回的租约
is the lease back from the front end now
when the set arrives the memcache server
会看一下租约，说一会儿，我没有租约
will look at the lease and say wait a
minute I you don't have a lease for this
如果所有这些都适合此键，则该键会失效，我将忽略此设置，因为
key all right invalid if these fit this
key I'm gonna ignore this set so because
租约是因为这些删除之一是在其中之一之前出现的
the lease has been because one of these
if one of these deletes came in before
无效的集合和内存缓存服务器
the set this sees to be invalid in
invalidated and the memcache server
会忽略此设置，这意味着该键将只留下
would ignore this set and that would
mean that the key would note just stay
从Memcache和下一个尝试读取该密钥的客户端中丢失
missing from memcache and the next
client that tried to read that key
您会发现Miss会立即从数据库中读取新数据，并且会
you'll get a Miss would read the fresh
data now from the database and would
将其安装在内存缓存中，大概是第二次安装
install it in memcache and presumably
the second time around
第二个读者的租约将是有效的，嗯，实际上您应该问
the second readers lease would be valid
um you may and indeed you should ask
顺序不同的原因是什么，所以假设这些删除
what happened that the order is
different so supposing these deletes
而不是在集合之前发生这些删除，而是
instead of happening before the set
these deletes were instead to have
我想确保该方案在设置之后仍然发生，然后如何
happen after the set I want to make sure
this scheme still works then and so how
那么事情就会发生，因为如果这些Dilys迟到了，
things would play out then is that since
if these Dilys were late happened after
设置Memcache服务器不会将其从签证表中删除
the set the memcache server wouldn't
delete these from its table of visas
当场景出现时，索利斯仍会在那里，是的，我们确实会那时
Solis would still be there when the set
came and yes indeed we would still then
它会接受我们将键设置为陈旧值的设置，但我们
it would accept the setting we would be
setting key to a stale value but our
假设是这次删除已延迟，这意味着
assumption was this time that the
deletes had been late and that means the
Dilys还没有到达，当它们删除时，它们会留下来
Dilys are yet to arrive and when they
when these deletes arrive then this stay
theta上的数据将被从缓存中删除，因此过时的日期将在
on theta will be knocked out of the
cache and so the stale date will be in
缓存会更长一点，但是我们不会遇到过时的情况
the cache a little bit longer but we
won't have this situation where stale
数据无限期地位于缓存中，并且永不删除
data is sitting in the cache
indefinitely and never deleted
莉萨机械有任何问题，好的，请给您总结一下
any questions
lissa machinery okay um to wrap up you
将这个系统视为很多复杂的系统当然是公平的
it's certainly fair to view this system
a lot of the complexity of the system as
源于这样的事实，那就是它拼凑在一起，
stemming from the fact that it was sort
of put together out of pieces that
彼此不认识，例如memcached他会很好
didn't know about each other like it
would be nice for example memcached he
知道数据库，我了解内存缓存D和数据库的种类
knew about the database I'm understand
memcache D and the database kind of
在一致性计划方面进行了合作，也许Facebook可以在
cooperated in a consistency scheme and
perhaps if Facebook could have at the
从一开始，您就知道预言了事情将如何发展。
very beginning you know predicted the
how things would play out on what the
问题将会是，如果他们有足够的工程师来工作，他们
problems would be and if they have had
enough engineers to work on it they
从一开始就可以建立一个可以提供所有
could have from the beginning built a
system that could provide both all the
他们需要的高性能多数据中心复制分区
things they needed high-performance
multi data center replication partition
一切都在这样做的公司中
and everything and they're having
companies that have done that so the
我知道的例子最类似于
example I know of that sort of most
directly comparable to the system in
这篇论文是，如果您关心这些东西，您可能想看看它
this paper is that if you care about
this stuff you might want to look at it
是Yahoo的花生存储系统，其设计从头开始，
is Yahoo's peanuts storage system which
in a sort of designed from scratch and
您知道许多细节上都不同，但是它确实提供了多站点
you know different different in many
details but it does provide multi-site
复制具有一致性和良好的性能，因此可以做到
replication with consistency and good
performance so it's possible to do
更好，但是您知道所有存在的问题都存在
better but you know all the issues are
present that's just had a more
集成的也许优雅的解决方案
integrated perhaps elegant set of
solutions
因此，对于本文而言，对我们而言，至少对他们而言
the takeaway so for us from this paper
one is that for them at least and for
许多大型操作缓存对于高生存至关重要至关重要
many big operations caching is vital
absolutely vital for to survive high
加载和缓存并不仅仅是减少延迟，它还需要更多
load and the caching is not so much
about reducing latency it's much more
隐藏相对较慢的巨大负载
about hiding enormous load from
relatively slow
缓存实际上是为Facebook做的存储服务器正在隐藏排序
storage servers that's what a cache is
really doing for Facebook is hiding sort
隐藏几乎所有来自数据库服务器的负载的另一个收获是
of concealing almost all the load from
the database servers another takeaway is
在大型系统中，您始终需要考虑缓存
that you always in big systems you
always need to be thinking about caching
与控制，对不起，分区与复制，我的意思是您需要一些方法
versus control versus sorry partition
versus replication I mean you need ways
正式或非正式地决定您的资源量
of either formally or informally sort of
deciding how much your resources are
将致力于分区以及复制多少，最后
going to be devoted to partitioning and
how much to replication and finally
理想情况下，您将能够从一开始就在本文中做得更好
ideally you'd be able to do a better job
in this paper about from the beginning
集成不同的存储层以实现良好的一致性
integrating the different storage layers
in order to achieve good consistency
好吧，这就是我要说的，请问我问题
okay that is all I have to say please
ask me questions if you have